Welcome everybody to Intro to HTML.
欢迎大家来到 HTML 简介课程
In this fabulous course,
在这节课程中
we're going to take you through the fundamentals and
我们会带你了解创建一个网页
building blocks to create a web page,
所需的基础知识和元素
and ultimately for you to become your own developer.
最终培养你成为一个独立的开发人员
The first step is to learn HTML which will let us lay out our elements,
第一步需要学习的是 HTML 它可以让我们对元素进行布局
and then we'll go through some CSS which will allow us to style our elements.
接着我们会开始学习 CSS 它让我们可以给页面上的元素添加样式
Then will go even further and we'll do some advanced stuff,
然后我们会进一步完成一些高级的内容
so we can create layouts and we can set
我们会创建一些布局样式
each of our elements to be distributed how we want.
把元素分布成我们想要的结果
This is how we put together the pieces to make a pixel perfect web page,
这就是我们把各个部分拼凑成一个整块 并创造出完美像素级页面的方法
and you are going to be able to do just that. Let's hop in.
你将会有能力去实现它 让我们开始吧
So to start Intro to HTML,
我们首先来认识 HTML
let's ask the big questions,
我们先思考几个大问题
like what does HTML stand for?
例如 HTML 的全称是什么？
What is HTML?
什么是 HTML？
Why even learn HTML?
为什么要学习 HTML？
Well, HTML is the basis for all web pages.
好吧 HTML 是所有网页的基础
Without HTML, you would not be able to organize
没有 HTML 你就没办法在页面上
text or add pictures or videos to your web page's.
组织你的文字 图片或者视频内容等等
HTML is the start of all you need to understand and build engaging web pages.
如果你想要创造出酷炫的网站 HTML 就是你的起点
Now, what it stands for, get ready.
那么 HTML 的全称是什么呢？请集中注意力
Hyper Text Markup Language, HTML.
超文本标记语言 (Hyper Text Markup Language) HTML
Hyper Text Markup Language. Got that?
超文本标记语言 (Hyper Text Markup Language) 知道了吧？
You will soon. Hypertext implies that it uses the HTTP portion of internet markup,
超文本意味着它使用了互联网标记 HTTP 部分
meaning the code you write is annotated with keywords.
也就是说你的代码中会使用一些关键字进行注释
These keywords allow the browser to read your code
浏览器可以通过这些关键字读取你的代码
and then to produce it as a set of visual experiences for a user.
并为用户呈现出对应的视觉效果
The fact that HTML ends in
之所以 HTML 以语言结尾是因为
language implies that it can be read both by a person and a computer.
它既可以被电脑识别 也可以直接被我们识别出来
Like any language HTML comes with a set of rules.
和其他语言一样 HTML 也有一定的规则
So before we get into those rules,
在我们了解这些规则之前
let's take a little bit of a higher level picture at HTML and say that HTML
让我们从一个更宏观的角度来看待 HTML
is a sequence of tags that tell web browsers how to make or show a web page.
HTML 就是通过一系列标签告诉浏览器如何生成和显示 Web 页面
An example of a tag might be a paragraph tag,
比如一个段落标签
which tells the browser that the next data that
它会告诉浏览器接下来
follows should be a paragraph of text shown in the browser.
需要显示的数据应该是一段文字
Learning some useful and exceptional HTML tags,
学习一些实用的、主要的 HTML 标签
it's a great way to begin constructing your web pages.
是开始搭建一个 Web 页面的比较好的方式
So that's just what we're going to do,
这也是我们即将要做的事情
we are going to hop in and we're going to look at what
我们要开始了 我们会看看
the elements are that make up this HTML.
组成了这些 HTML 标签的元素都是什么
But lastly, before we do that, why HTML?
但是 在那之前 还有一个问题 为什么选择 HTML？
Why would you want to learn HTML?
为什么要学习 HTML 呢？
Well, HTML is the standard markup language for creating web pages and web apps.
因为 HTML 现在是开发 Web 网页和 Web app 的标准标记语言
You can put HTML with two other programming languages,
你可以把 HTML 和 CSS 和 JavaScript 两门语言结合起来
CSS and JavaScript, to create full stack interactive web experiences.
来创造出完整的交互式 Web 体验
Those three come together, CSS, JavaScript,
这三种语言构成了一个完整的网站
and HTML to create the foundation of the Web
而 HTML 则是其中的最基础部分